[{"answer": "You can keep it", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "How late do you stay open", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " I haven't been on the job five minutes and already she's making advances to me.  Not that I care", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "No wonder he passed away.  I'd like to be with you to the very end. Can't you see what I'm trying to tell you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I'll tell you what I'll do.  I'll give you Mrs. my friend as security.  or my jackknife.  If you want my advice, you'll take the jackknife... I've a better proposition...  Make it", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " Why yes.  I met you at the dog races", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " We're not allowed to tell a dirty joke HAIL, HAIL, that plac", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " If we should choose to chew, we'll be pursued", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " So everyone beware Who's crooked or unfai", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": " The husband steps outsid", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Here I am, Father..", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " His Excellency's car", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No, but my dog he's a got millions of them", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He used to be a bloodhound but he's anemic", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Half watch dog", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "my friend, he's only got one eye", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't call him, I whistle", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I don't know much about dogs but you ought to be on the end of a leash", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What do you whistle", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "'At'", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, but I shot some ducks", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "That's no good.  I like to work on the outside.  I must have something easy", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't wanna work at all", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "In that case you'll have to take a civil service examination", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Well, if you wanna work in the pos", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " You know, I'd be lost without a telephone.  Now", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You get half mine and I get half yours", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What do I get", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I don't want to buy ammunition", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "You get half mine and I get half yours", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Then we've gotta start one. Do you know how to start a war", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I don't want to buy ammunition", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Sure, that's easy.  You gotta insult somebody", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " That's ", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You was insulted, but you don't know it", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You've got a brain after all", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Why didn't his niece slap your face", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "He'", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "She did", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Why didn't his niece slap your face", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "What did you say to her", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "All I can offer you is a Rufus over your head", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I wouldn't know what to say either if I was in your place.  Maybe you can suggest something", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Oh", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Was it", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": " No, that wasn't it..", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": " No... it was a seven letter word", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": " Now", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's not fair", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "No. Sevent", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "We gotta two battalions and one Frenchman", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I wish you were still working for me, so I could ask you to resign. How're ya fixed for cavalry", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "That's funny, we've got five thousand horses but no men", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "Anything else?", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": " Fine.  We'll throw in the matches before we make the delivery.  By the way, how're you fixed for spys", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "That's easy, I'll get him for you wholesale", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I can't do it right away", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": " Hail, hail, that place...  Land of the brave and free", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "We really think he should be king", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "My dad is much too great for his position without a question.  I'd like to offer this with your permission as a suggestio", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "I really think he should be king", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "We really think he should be king", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "He should be king", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "And everything", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "He should be king", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "He should be king", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "He should be king", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "King my friend was game he gave each Girl his name to number them would make a list that long I'll bet his thousand wives led miserable lives if the king can do no wrong", "docId": "Duck-Soup.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "They think I should", "qsentId": 70}]